<site>
	<contentareas>
		<contentarea id="nav1">
			<![CDATA[Proudly Serving<br/>[LONGKEY]]]>
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="nav2">Security Systems [SHORTKEY]</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="nav3">Security Cameras [SHORTKEY]</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="nav4">Surveillance Cameras [SHORTKEY]</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="nav5">Access Control [SHORTKEY]</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="home1">Security Systems in [LONGKEY]</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="home2">
			<![CDATA[
			<h2>Security Systems Installations in [LONGKEY] by SkyNet</h2>
			<p>With theft statistics at an all-time high, protecting your business or property with an advanced security system has become more important than ever. While there is an increasing demand for security systems, the implementation of them can prove quite costly. SkyNet Security Systems offers its clients a perfect, cost effective solution.</p>
			<p>At SkyNet Security Systems we excel at catering our surveillance security systems to the varied needs of our commercial and residential clients.</p>
			<p>With over 15 years of industry experience and 1,000 clients nationwide, you can rest assured that we have a solution for you! Whether you're in the market for a new system or you're looking to improve, repair or replace your existing system, you'll find our reputation for service speaks for itself.</p>
			]]>
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="system1">
			SkyNet Security Systems is your preferred partner for security system installation throughout the [LONGKEY] area.
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="system2">
			<![CDATA[
			<h2>Residential Security Systems in [SHORTKEY]</h2>
			<p>Studies indicate that the economic recession sparked growth in at least one arena: the national crime rate. With theft statistics at an all-time high, protecting your business or property with an advanced security system has become more important than ever, and there is no more affordable solution than SkyNet Security's wireless security system. If you want to prevent unnecessary loss, effectively manage emergency situations, and monitor your property or business remotely, a digital video surveillance system is the right solution for you.</p>
			<p>Our experienced technicians strive to provide exceptional security system design and installation services of innovative home security systems that are cost-effective, easy-to-use and feature high-quality industry components such as:<br/> 
			<ul>
			<li>Wireless Alarm Systems</li>
			<li>Wired Alarm Systems</li>
			<li>Monitoring Services</li>
			<li>Video Security Cameras</li>
			</ul>
			</p>
			]]>
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="system3">
			<![CDATA[
			<h2>Commercial Security Systems in [SHORTKEY]</h2>
			<p>A Commercial SkyNet Security System will assist your company in protecting your business and your employees. Our sophisticated security and surveillance systems utilize high-quality closed-circuit television (CCTV) and sophisticated alarm-system products to provide you with innovative, yet simple-to-use, commercial security features and cost-effective peace of mind.</p>  
			<p>Our Security Systems incorporate:<br/>
			<ul>
			<li>Digital Video Recorders</li>
			<li>Network Video Recorders</li>
			<li>Remote-Viewing Surveillance</li>
			<li>Electronic Access Control</li>
			</ul>
			</p>
			]]>
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="camera1">
		  SkyNet Security Systems is the professional source for security cameras in the [LONGKEY] area.
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="camera2">
		  <![CDATA[
				<p>SkyNet Security Systems has the security cameras you need for your home security system or business surveillance system.   Whether you are looking to keep burglars our of your home or monitor your business property and employees while you are away, our security camera experts are here to help give you that extra peace of mind that you deserve. </p>
				<p>SkyNet Security Systems offers and installs a complete line of surveillance cameras in a wide variety of lens sizes and a full range of resolutions. Our professional quality cameras offer low-illumination, infrared, megapixel, IP, and wide angle capabilities. We also offer dome, full-body, bullet, and pan-tilt-zoom cameras to help meet unique installation needs.</p>
				]]>
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="surv1">
			SkyNet Security System is your source for high-quality, professional-grade surveillance security systems in [LONGKEY].
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="surv2">
			<![CDATA[
      <p>As surveillance camera experts, we at SkyNet Security Systems pride ourselves on the fact that we sell only professional grade lines of home security cameras and business surveillance systems from top manufacturers.  We consistently provide you with surveillance cameras, video recorders and security systems that are cost effective and field-proven.</p> 
      <h2>24/7 Coverage of Your Most Important Assets</h2>
      <p>A video surveillance system from SkyNet Security Systems provide you with round-the-clock peace of mind that can also increase productivity at your workplace while you are away. Connect to your video cameras from anywhere & anytime and see what you've been missing.  Call to speak with a video surveillance specialist and we will deliver an effective video security & access control system that you can rely on.</p>
      <h2>Protect & Prevent Crime With Video Surveillance</h2>
      <p>Protect your Business, Employees & Customers. Prevent vandalism, crime and unnecessary loss, effectively manage emergency situations, and monitor your property or business remotely, a digital video surveillance system is the right solution for you. A SkyNet Security consultant can help you choose from a wide range of products and help you create a customized solution that fits your specific needs.</p>
			]]>
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="ac1">
			SkyNet Security System is your source for high-quality, professional-grade access control systems in [LONGKEY].
		</contentarea>
		<contentarea id="ac2">
			<![CDATA[
			]]>
		</contentarea>
	</contentareas>
</site>

